American Pie Presents: Girls' Rules is a comedy film directed by Mike Elliott.
It's Senior year at East Great Falls.
Annie, Kayla, Michelle, and Stephanie decide to harness their girl power and band
together to get what they want their last year of high school.
Annie, played by Madison Pettis.
Stephanie, played by Lizze Broadway.
Kayla, played by Piper Curda.
Michelle, played by Natasha Behnam.
Grant, played by Darren Barnet.
Emmett, played by Zachary Gordon.
American Pie Presents: Girls' Rules is a 2020 American
sex comedy film directed by Mike Elliott.
It is the fifth installment of the American Pie Presents film series, a spin-off
of the American Pie franchise and the ninth overall installment.
It is the first film in the franchise to not feature Eugene
Levy and also the first to contain no nudity.
The film serves as a standalone sequel, revolving around Steve
Stifler's relative Stephanie (Lizze Broadway) and her friends.
The film was released on demand and DVD on October
6, 2020, by Universal Pictures.
It was released on Blu-ray on September 7, 2021.
The film explores themes of high school, teen movie, spin off, pie, ambivalent.
The tone is lighthearted.